Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - B
        - Blahzay Blahzay - Danger, 1995; SR-11826; Blahzay Blahzay (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11825. Different discs
          Catalog # 697 120 081-1; A-side Matrix # 697-120-081-1A
        - Blair, John - Momma said shut-up, 1985; SR-11827; Blair, John (Box 191)
          Catalog # SAK-001; A-side Matrix # SAK-001-A
          SAKB Records
        - Blak Czer - Who got the glock; Stick up, 1994; SR-11828; Blak Czer (Box 191)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0288; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0288-1A
        - Blak Panta - Do what u want, 1995; SR-11829; Blak Panta (Box 191)
          Catalog # TB 677; A-side Matrix # TB 677-A-RE1
        - Blak Panta - Do what u want, 1995; SR-11830; Blak Panta (Box 191)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # RAG-0002-A
        - Blak Prophetz - With FX, 2002; SR-11831; Blak Prophetz (Box 191)
          Catalog # FJ001; A-side Matrix # FJ 01 A
          Fatt Jointz Rekordz
        - Blak, Silas - Time called think; How obnoxious; I know why, 1998; SR-12796; Blak, Silas (Box 191)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # 6304 SLOW-1 S43394
          Slow Burn
        - Blak Twang - The queen head, 1995; SR-11832; Blak Twang (Box 191)
          Catalog # SNM 005; A-side Matrix # SNM-005-A1
          Sound of Money
        - Blak Twang - Real estate, 1996; SR-11833; Blak Twang (Box 191)
          Catalog # SNM 007; A-side Matrix # SNM 007-A1
        - Blake & Hines - Blake & Hines, 1987; SR-11834; Blake & Hines (Box 191)
          Catalog # 6224ML; A-side Matrix # 6224 ML A -15B ZAS
        - Blake & Hines - Sherry, 1986; SR-11835; Blake & Hines (Box 191)
          Catalog # PR-199; A-side Matrix # PR 199 A67751-67747-15A ZAQ #12
        - Blake, Paul - Rub-a-dub soldier, 1984; SR-11837; Blake, Paul; Blood Fire Posse (Box 191)
          Catalog # RAS 7007; A-side Matrix # RAS-7007-A
          Real Authentic Sound
        - Teemour - Don Blakka (Disc one), 1999; SR-11838; Teemour (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11839. Double album
          Catalog # 3984 27876 1; A-side Matrix # 398427876-1 A
          East West France
        - Teemour - Don Blakka (Disc two), 1999; SR-11839; Teemour (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11838. Double album
          Catalog # 3984 27876 1; A-side Matrix # 398427876-1 C
        - B.L.A.M. - Moo-la rules, SR-11840; B.L.A.M.; Simpson, Tim (Box 191)
          Catalog # BBM 9105; A-side Matrix # BBM-9105-A
          Big Brother Records
        - Blanchard, Gerard - Elle voulait revoir sa normandie, 1987; SR-11841; Blanchard, Gerard (Box 191)
          Catalog # 885 535-1; A-side Matrix # 222 8855351 A
          Barclay
        - Blanco, Nel - Make it bop, SR-11842; Blanco, Nel; Sam Sam (Box 191)
          Catalog # AV135; A-side Matrix # AV-135-A
          AV8 Records
        - Blancmange - That's love, that is it, 1983; SR-11843; Blancmange (Box 191)
          Catalog # 0-20282; A-side Matrix # B-20438-SHI
        - Blancmange - Lose your love; Ave Maria, 1985; SR-11844; Blancmange (Box 191)
          Catalog # 0-20412; A-side Matrix # B-22129-SHI
        - Blanket of Secrecy - Ears have walls, 1982; SR-11845; Blanket of Secrecy (Box 191)
          Catalog # 1-23722; A-side Matrix # B-17031-ASHI
        - Blaq, Rufus - Give it to me daddy; Out of sight (yo) remix, 1998; SR-11846; Blaq, Rufus (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11847. 2 copies
          Catalog # PSPRO 00690; A-side Matrix # PSPRO 00690 A -WE1
          Perspective Records
        - Blaq, Rufus - Give it to me daddy; Out of sight (yo) remix, 1998; SR-11847; Blaq, Rufus (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11846. 2 copies
        - Blaq, Rufus - Make it hot, 1998; SR-11848; Blaq, Rufus (Box 191)
          Catalog # PSPRO 00691; A-side Matrix # PSPRO 00691 A1 -WE1
        - Blaque - 808, 1999; SR-11849; Blaque (Box 191)
          Catalog # 44 78858; A-side Matrix # XSS-78858A-1ARJ
        - Blaque - 808, 1999; SR-11850; Blaque (Box 191)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # DCHARLES
        - Blast Zone - Mary had a little jam, 1988; SR-11851; Blast Zone (Box 191)
          Catalog # BBR-002; A-side Matrix # L-11352-BBR-002-A1
          Blip Blop Records
        - Blasters - Barefoot rock, 1983; SR-11852; Blasters (Box 191)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2017; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-32017-SHI
        - Blasters - The Blasters, 1981; SR-11853; Blasters (Box 191)
          Catalog # SR-109; A-side Matrix # SR-109-A
          Slash
        - Blasters - Over there (live at the venue, London), 1982; SR-11854; Blasters (Box 191)
          Catalog # 1-23735; A-side Matrix # B-17069-SH4
        - Blaze - Basic blaze (Disc one), 1998; SR-11855; Blaze (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11856. Double album
          Catalog # TRUE LP01; A-side Matrix # TRUE LP 01-A1
          True Recordings
        - Blaze - Basic blaze (Disc two), 1998; SR-11856; Blaze (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11855. Double album
          Catalog # TRUE LP01; A-side Matrix # TRUE LP 01-C1
        - Blaze - So special, 1990; SR-11857; Blaze (Box 191)
          Catalog # L33-1204; A-side Matrix # MOT-10489-FW1
        - Blige, Mary J - Be happy; Freak me, 2001; SR-11858; Blige, Mary J; Jodeci (Box 191)
          Catalog # None; A-side Matrix # HOT-001-A1
          Hot 97
        - Blaze - My beat, 2001; SR-11859; Blaze; Brown, Palmer (Box 191)
          Catalog # TB2230; A-side Matrix # TB-2230-A
        - Blaze, Jonny - Get it together, 2004; SR-11860; Blaze, Jonny; DJ Jonny Blaze (Box 191)
          Catalog # B1R-0009; A-side Matrix # B1R-0009-A
          Blaze One Records
          Baltimore, Maryland
        - Blendcrafters - Melody (Remix), 2004; SR-12797; Blendcrafters (Box 191)
          Catalog # UPA 3085-1; A-side Matrix # UPA 3085-1-A
          Up Above Records
          Long Beach, California
        - Bleu Davinci - Streets on lock, 2005; SR-11861; Bleu Davinci; Fabolous; Young Jeezy (Box 191)
          Catalog # KOC-12-5865; A-side Matrix # KOC-12-5865-A
          BMF Entertainment
        - B.L.H.U.N.T. - Choke, 1998; SR-11862; B.L.H.U.N.T. (Box 191)
          Catalog # PRO 74; A-side Matrix # PRO-74-A RE-1
        - Blige, Mary J - Real love (remix), SR-11863; Blige, Mary J (Box 191)
          Catalog # MJ-01; A-side Matrix # DR-20512-M-A-MJ-01
        - Blige, Mary J - Inside Mary, 2000; SR-11864; Blige, Mary J; Big Fella (Box 191)
          Catalog # IMJ 003; A-side Matrix # IMJ-001 A-1
        - Blige, Mary J - Everything (Disc one), 1997; SR-11865; Blige, Mary J (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11866. Double album
          Catalog # MCA24 55354; A-side Matrix # MCA-12955 A
        - Blige, Mary J - Everything (Disc two), 1997; SR-11866; Blige, Mary J (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11865. Double album
        - Blige, Mary J - The breakthrough (Disc one), 2005; SR-11867; Blige, Mary J (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11868. Double album
          Catalog # B0005722-01; A-side Matrix # B0005722-01-A
        - Blige, Mary J - The breakthrough (Disc two), 2005; SR-11868; Blige, Mary J (Box 191)
          In same jacket as # SR-11867. Double album
          Catalog # B0005722-01; A-side Matrix # B0005722-01 RE-1 C
        - Blige, Mary J - Family affair, 2000; SR-11869; Blige, Mary J (Box 191)
          Catalog # 088 155 859-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR-25375-1-A
        - Blige, Mary J - Your child, 2000; SR-11870; Blige, Mary J (Box 191)
          Catalog # MCAR 25127-1; A-side Matrix # MCA 13731
        - Blige, Mary J - Be without you, 2005; SR-11871; Blige, Mary J (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11872. 2 copies
          Catalog # GEFR26230-1; A-side Matrix # GEFR 26230-1A
        - Blige, Mary J - Be without you, 2005; SR-11872; Blige, Mary J (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11871. 2 copies
        - Blige, Mary J - Let no man put asunder; Deep as; Inside (Disc one), 1999; SR-11873; Blige, Mary J (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11874. Double album
          Catalog # MCA8P 4472; A-side Matrix # MCA 13650
        - Blige, Mary J - Let no man put asunder; Deep as; Inside (Disc two), 1999; SR-11874; Blige, Mary J (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11873. Double album
          Catalog # MCA8P 4472; A-side Matrix # MCA 13648
        - Blige, Mary J - Let no man put asunder; As, 2001; SR-11875; Blige, Mary J; Michael, George (Box 192)
          Catalog # MJB 008; A-side Matrix # MJB 008 A
        - Blige, Mary J - No more drama, 2001; SR-11876; Blige, Mary J (Box 192)
          Catalog # MCAR-25619-1; A-side Matrix # MCAR-25619-1A
        - Blind Dog Stares - Thru the fence; Troller tanz, 1981; SR-11877; Blind Dog Stares (Box 192)
          Catalog # GUI 100; A-side Matrix # GUI-100-A
          Guillotine Records
        - Bliss - Fun, 1981; SR-11878; Bliss (Box 192)
          Catalog # RC-302; A-side Matrix # RC-302-A
          Rap City Records
          Westbury, New York
        - Blitz Mob - Die organisation (Disc one), 1995; SR-11879; Blitz Mob (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11880. Double album
          Catalog # BV 1010-2; A-side Matrix # EFA-LP-61010 A
          Blitz Vinyl
        - Blitz Mob - Die organisation (Disc two), 1995; SR-11880; Blitz Mob (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11879. Double album
          Catalog # BV 1010-2; A-side Matrix # EFA-LP-61010 C
        - Blondie - Rapture, 1981; SR-11881; Blondie (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11882. 2 copies
          Catalog # CHS 12 2485; A-side Matrix # 634 CHS 122485 A4 DM POLYGRAM
        - Blondie - Rapture, 1981; SR-11882; Blondie (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11881. 2 copies
          Catalog # CHS 12 2485; A-side Matrix # 634 CHS 122485 A5 DM1 POLYGRAM
        - Blondie - Who's gonna cry; Maria; No exit, 1999; SR-11883; Blondie; Loud Allstars (Box 192)
          Catalog # RDAB-65699-1; A-side Matrix # RDAB-65699-1-A
        - Blondie - Heart of glass, 1978; SR-11884; Blondie (Box 192)
          Catalog # CDS-2275; A-side Matrix # CDS-2275-A-1B
        - Blondy, Alpha - Sweet fanta diallo, 1987; SR-11885; Blondy, Alpha (Box 192)
          Catalog # SP 1355; A-side Matrix # SP 1355 A 21
          Pathé Marconi EMI
        - Blood Clot - Can u dig it, 1993; SR-11886; Blood Clot (Box 192)
          Catalog # SC-7005; A-side Matrix # SC 7005-A
          Sand Castle Records
        - Blood of Abraham - Future profits, 1993; SR-11887; Blood of Abraham (Box 192)
          Catalog # 88561-5502-1; A-side Matrix # 5502-1A
        - Blood of Abraham - Stabbed by the steeple; Niggaz and jewz, 1993; SR-11888; Blood of Abraham (Box 192)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0246; A-side Matrix # RPROLP 0246 A
        - Blood of Abraham - Future profits, 1994; SR-11889; Blood of Abraham (Box 192)
          Catalog # RPROLP-0268; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0268 A
        - Blood, Sweat & Tears - Blood, Sweat & Tears greatest hits, 1972; SR-11890; Blood, Sweat & Tears (Box 192)
          Catalog # KC 31170; A-side Matrix # P AL 31170 3A
        - Blood, Sweat & Tears - Blood, Sweat & Tears, 1968; SR-11891; Blood, Sweat & Tears (Box 192)
          Catalog # CS 9720; A-side Matrix # XSM137878-1AD
        - Blood, Sweat & Tears - More than ever, 1976; SR-11892; Blood, Sweat & Tears (Box 192)
          Catalog # PC 34233; A-side Matrix # P AL 34233-1A
        - Blood, Sweat & Tears - Nuclear blues, 1980; SR-11893; Blood, Sweat & Tears (Box 192)
          Catalog # MCA-3227; A-side Matrix # MCA-2151
        - Bloodstone - Instant love, 1984; SR-11894; Bloodstone (Box 192)
          Catalog # AS 1888; A-side Matrix # XSS-169702-1C
          T-Neck
        - Bloodstone - My love grows stronger, 1982; SR-11895; Bloodstone (Box 192)
          Catalog # 4Z9-03403; A-side Matrix # 4Z9-03403-3-AB
        - Bloodsuckas - Radio athletico, 1996; SR-11896; Bloodsuckas (Box 192)
          Catalog # JAZID 133 T; A-side Matrix # JAZID-133T-A1
          Acid Jazz
        - Bloomsday - Fortuny, 1990; SR-11897; Bloomsday (Box 192)
          Catalog # 211 191; A-side Matrix # 010 DM211191 A-1 C
        - Blount, Carlton - A day without love, 1989; SR-11898; Blount, Carlton (Box 192)
          Catalog # SN-1003; A-side Matrix # SN-1002-A
          So-New Records
          East Orange, New Jersey
        - Family Blaque - Wade in the water, 1990; SR-11899; Family Blaque (Box 192)
          Catalog # KC-166; A-side Matrix # KC166-A
          Kendon Records
        - Blount, Tanya - Hold on, 1994; SR-11900; Blount, Tanya (Box 192)
          Catalog # PR12 6885-1; A-side Matrix # PR12-6885-1AS/HS
        - Blow, Curtis - America, 1985; SR-11901; Blow, Curtis (Box 192)
          Catalog # 884 079-1; A-side Matrix # 884-079-1-AS-ES-1
        - Blow - Change (makes you want to hustle), 1988; SR-11902; Blow (Box 192)
          Catalog # TENZ 245; A-side Matrix # TENZ 245 A-1U-1-1
        - Blow, Curtis - The breaks, 1980; SR-11903; Blow, Curtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11904. Different discs"Richmond pressing"
          Catalog # MDS-4010; A-side Matrix # MDS-4010-A-PRO-R-2-1-1
        - Blow, Curtis - The breaks, 1980; SR-11904; Blow, Curtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11903. Different discs
          Catalog # MDS-4010; A-side Matrix # MDS-4010-A-9
        - Blow, Kurtis - Chillin' at the spot, 1994; SR-11905; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11906. Different discs
          Catalog # SPV 50-39925 MS; A-side Matrix # 0 50 399-25 A
          Public Attack
        - Fullmoon - Spoonful of soul, 1994; SR-11906; Fullmoon; Soul SK (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11905. Different discs
          Catalog # PA 50-39895; A-side Matrix # 503 9895 A
        - Blow, Kurtis - Party time?, 1983; SR-11907; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11908. 2 copies
          Catalog # 422-812 757-1 M-1; A-side Matrix # 422-812757-1 AS-HRM
        - Blow, Kurtis - Party time?, 1983; SR-11908; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11907. 2 copies
        - Blow, Kurtis - Kurtis Blow, 1980; SR-11909; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11910. 2 copies
          Catalog # SRM-1-3854; A-side Matrix # SRM-1-3854-PRC-R A-2-11-1
        - Blow, Kurtis - Kurtis Blow, 1980; SR-11910; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11909. 2 copies
        - Blow, Kurtis - Christmas rappin', 1979; SR-11911; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          Catalog # MDS-4009; A-side Matrix # MDS-4009-A-K1
        - Blow, Kurtis - If I ruled the world, 1985; SR-11912; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          Catalog # 884 269-1; A-side Matrix # 884269-1 2-58547ES
        - Blow, Kurtis - The Bronx, 1986; SR-11913; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11914. 2 copies
          Catalog # PRO 476-1; A-side Matrix # PRPO-476-1-AS-ES
        - Blow, Kurtis - The Bronx, 1986; SR-11914; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11913. 2 copies
        - Blow, Kurtis - Ego trip, 1984; SR-11915; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          Catalog # PRO 328-1; A-side Matrix # PRO 328-1-2-57994-ALD
        - Blow, Kurtis - Starlife; Way out west, 1981; SR-11916; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          Catalog # MDS-4012; A-side Matrix # MDS-4012 2-57407-PRC-C-1 1-1 A
        - Blow, Kurtis - Hard times, 1980; SR-11917; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          Catalog # MK 162; A-side Matrix # MK-162 2-56182-PW1
        - Blow, Kurtis - Nervous, 1983; SR-11918; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          Catalog # 814 484-1; A-side Matrix # 814-1-2-57605-A-LONG-PRC-C1-1-1
        - Blow, Kurtis - Party time, 1983; SR-11919; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11920. 2 copies
          Catalog # MK 248; A-side Matrix # MK-248-PRC-C1-1 A
        - Blow, Kurtis - Party time, 1983; SR-11920; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          In same jacket as # SR-11919. 2 copies
        - Blow, Kurtis - I'm chillin', 1986; SR-11921; Blow, Kurtis (Box 192)
          Catalog # 888-004-1; A-side Matrix # 888-004-1-AS-3
        - Blow, Kurtis - Basketball; It’s the game, 1984; SR-11922; Blow, Kurtis; MacDonald, Ralph (Box 192)
          Catalog # 881 529-1; A-side Matrix # 881-529-1-84-NP-6759-HRM
        - Blow Monkeys - Animal magic, 1986; SR-11923; Blow Monkeys (Box 192)
          Catalog # PL 70910; A-side Matrix # B-3401A-2
        - Blow Monkeys - Wicked ways, 1986; SR-11924; Blow Monkeys (Box 192)
          Catalog # JW-14424; A-side Matrix # PW-14424-C-2
        - Blow Monkeys - Digging your scene, 1986; SR-11925; Blow Monkeys (Box 192)
          Catalog # JW-14327; A-side Matrix # PW-14327-A-1
        - Blow Monkeys - It doesn't have to be this way, 1987; SR-11926; Blow Monkeys (Box 192)
          Catalog # 6281-1-RDAB; A-side Matrix # 6281-1-RDA-1
        - Blow Monkeys - Springtime for the world, 1990; SR-11927; Blow Monkeys (Box 192)
          Catalog # PT 43624; A-side Matrix # PT 43624 A-2J-1-1
        - Blowfly - Porno freak, 1981; SR-11928; Blowfly (Box 192)
          Catalog # 2036; A-side Matrix # WW-20 36-A
          Weird World
          Hialeah, Florida
        - Blowfly - Funk you! Volume 4, 1984; SR-11929; Blowfly (Box 193)
          Catalog # FY-8401; A-side Matrix # FY 8401-A
          Metrovynil
        - Blowfly - Blowfly's Christmas party, 1980; SR-11930; Blowfly (Box 193)
          Catalog # 453; A-side Matrix # TKD-453-A-AM
          T.K. Disco
        - Blowfly - Blowfly on tour '86, 1986; SR-11931; Blowfly (Box 193)
          Catalog # LP-104; A-side Matrix # OOPS!!!-104-A
          Oops! Records
        - Blowfly - Zodiac party, 1978; SR-11932; Blowfly (Box 193)
          Catalog # LP-2031; A-side Matrix # WW-2031-A
        - Blowfly - Oldies but goodies, 1976; SR-11933; Blowfly (Box 193)
          Catalog # WW-2026; A-side Matrix # WW-2026-A
        - Blu - My ol' lady, 1995; SR-11934; Blu (Box 193)
          Catalog # 374631281-1; A-side Matrix # 37463 128-1-A
        - Blu - My ol' lady (remixes), 1995; SR-11935; Blu (Box 193)
          Catalog # 374631336-1; A-side Matrix # 37463 1336 1 A-SP1
        - Blu - Hide and go get it (remixes), 1995; SR-11936; Blu (Box 193)
          Catalog # 374631289-1; A-side Matrix # 37463-1289-1A-SP-1
        - Blu Peter - I bring you luv, 1997; SR-11937; Blu Peter (Box 193)
          Catalog # 12REACT 110; A-side Matrix # 12REACT 110-AA2
          React
        - Blue 12 - Everyday people, 1969; SR-11938; Blue 12 (Box 193)
          Catalog # PL-8703; A-side Matrix # PL 8703 A
          Partyline Records
        - Blue Amazon - And then the rain falls, 1997; SR-11939; Blue Amazon (Box 193)
          In same jacket as # SR-11940. Double album
          Catalog # SM-9063-0; A-side Matrix # SM-9036-A
        - Blue Amazon - And then the rain falls, 1997; SR-11940; Blue Amazon (Box 193)
          In same jacket as # SR-11939. Double album
          Catalog # SM-9063-0; A-side Matrix # SM-9036-C
        - Blue Boy - Trolley ride; Hip hop will never stop, 1993; SR-11941; Blue Boy (Box 193)
          Catalog # IR-80021; A-side Matrix # S-28308 RE-1
          Intense Records
        - Blue Boy - Thundering soca, 1984; SR-11942; Blue Boy (Box 193)
          Catalog # 0012AL; A-side Matrix # 0012AL-A
          Kalico Records
        - Blue Amazon - No other love, 1996; SR-11943; Blue Amazon (Box 193)
          Catalog # SM-9051-0; A-side Matrix # SM-9051-0A
        - Blue Boy - Caribbean magic, 1988; SR-11944; Blue Boy (Box 193)
          Catalog # BSR-BB-084; A-side Matrix # BSR BB 084-A
        - Blue Feather - Let's funk tonight, 1981; SR-11945; Blue Feather (Box 193)
          Catalog # FT 75002; A-side Matrix # 75002 A
          Tempesti
        - Blue Magic - Blue Magic, 1974; SR-11946; Blue Magic (Box 193)
          Catalog # SD 7038; A-side Matrix # ST-C-733001-B
        - Blue Mercedes - Love is the gun, 1980; SR-11947; Blue Mercedes (Box 193)
          Catalog # MCA-23879; A-side Matrix # MCA5027FOS-1
        - Blue Mercedes - I want to be your property, 1980; SR-11948; Blue Mercedes (Box 193)
          Catalog # MCA-23817; A-side Matrix # MCA 7407 ASR-2
        - Blue X - The next phase, 1999; SR-11949; Blue X (Box 193)
          Catalog # AV 098; A-side Matrix # AV-98-A
        - Blue Zone - On fire, 1987; SR-11950; Blue Zone (Box 193)
          Catalog # RHT 116; A-side Matrix # RHT 116A 4
          Arista
        - Blueprint - Ritespot, 1983; SR-11951; Blueprint (Box 193)
          Catalog # D-217; A-side Matrix # D217 A-1
        - Blues Brothers - The Blues Brothers (original soundtrack recording), 1980; SR-11952; Blues Brothers (Box 193)
          Catalog # SD 16017; A-side Matrix # STA-804498-C
        - Blvd. Mosse - U can't escape the hypeness, 1990; SR-11953; Blvd. Mosse (Box 193)
          Catalog # SM-1206; A-side Matrix # SM-1206-A
          Scorpio
        - Blythe, Arthur - Blythe spirit, 1981; SR-11954; Blythe, Arthur (Box 193)
          Catalog # AL 37427; A-side Matrix # AL 37427-1C
        - BM Dubs - The boy……, 2000; SR-11955; BM Dubs (Box 193)
          Catalog # JP010; A-side Matrix # JP 010 A2
          V Dubs
        - B.M.O.C. - Play that funk, 1988; SR-11956; B.M.O.C. (Box 193)
          Catalog # 0-20832; A-side Matrix # 0-20832-A-SHI
        - B.Nice - Rubber bands, SR-11957; B.Nice; C4; DJ Mars (Box 193)
          Catalog # FLR002; A-side Matrix # 9707X5C-A
          Funk Lab Records
          Tampa, Florida
        - Bo, Das - Türlich, türlich (sicher, dicker) (Disc one), 2000; SR-11959; Bo, Das (Box 193)
          In same jacket as # SR-11960. Double album
          Catalog # YPS 7031-0; A-side Matrix # B034737-01 A1
          Yo Mama's Recording
        - Bo, Das - Türlich, türlich (sicher, dicker) (Disc two), 2000; SR-11960; Bo, Das (Box 193)
          In same jacket as # SR-11959. Double album
          Catalog # YPS 7031-0; A-side Matrix # B034737-02 C2
        - Boss, Bo - Tequila, 1982; SR-11961; Boss, Bo (Box 193)
          Catalog # EMDS 6533; A-side Matrix # EMDS-6533-A
        - Bo, Eddie - The hook and sling, 1996; SR-11962; Bo, Eddie; Soul Finders (Box 193)
          Catalog # DEL LP 0006; A-side Matrix # DEL-LP-006-A
        - Bo, Eddie - The hook and sling, 1996; SR-11963; Bo, Eddie (Box 193)
          Catalog # DEL 129601; A-side Matrix # DEL-129601-A
        - Bo, Eddie - If it's good for you, it's good for you, 1996; SR-11964; Bo, Eddie (Box 193)
          Catalog # DEL 129603; A-side Matrix # DEL-129603-A
        - Bobby/Demo - More ounce, 1980; SR-11958; Bobby/Demo (Box 193)
          Catalog # D.K. 47; A-side Matrix # D.K.45-A
          Toronto, Canada
        - Bobby Ill's - My favorite song, 2000; SR-11965; Bobby Ill's (Box 193)
          Catalog # HMBC-2011; A-side Matrix # HMBC-2011-A
          HMBC Records Group
        - Bobien, Kenny - Let me show you (Disc one), 1998; SR-11966; Bobien, Kenny; DJ Spen; Karizma (Box 193)
          In same jacket as # SR-11967. Double album
          Catalog # SOW-425; A-side Matrix # SOW-425 A
          Soundmen on Wax
        - Bobien, Kenny - Let me show you (Disc two), 1998; SR-11967; Bobien, Kenny; DJ Spen; Karizma (Box 193)
          In same jacket as # SR-11966. Double album
          Catalog # SOW-425; A-side Matrix # SOW-425 C
        - Bobien, Kenny - I can't give you anything; Blessed, 1999; SR-11968; Bobien, Kenny (Box 193)
          Catalog # SOW-441; A-side Matrix # SOW-441 A
        - Bobo, Willie - Do what you want to do, 1971; SR-11969; Bobo, Willie (Box 193)
          Catalog # SXBS 7003; A-side Matrix # SXBS7003-A
          Sussex
        - Bobo - Bobo, 1979; SR-11970; Bobo (Box 193)
          Catalog # JC 36108; A-side Matrix # PAL 36108-1A
        - Bobo, Willie - Tomorrow is here, 1977; SR-11971; Bobo, Willie (Box 193)